buzzvil.com 2019-05-08

# Privacy policy - Buzzvil

## **Buzzvil Privacy Policy**

Buzzvil Co., Ltd. (Hereinafter referred to as “the Company”) takes personal information of users very seriously. This Privacy Policy details the main privacy policies that apply to data that the Company collects through Buzzvil’s advertising network business (“Service”).

Through this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”), the Company regards personal information of the users as important and inform them of the purpose and method of Company’s using the personal information provided by the users and the measures taken by the Company for protection of those personal information.

This Policy will be effective on the 25th day of May, 2018 and, in case of modification thereof, the Company will make public notice of it through posting it on the bulletin board of Company’s website or individual notice through sending mails, fax or e-mails.

#### **1\. About Buzzvil services**

Buzzvil offers online advertising network services. We provide personalized ads to mobile users of our partnered publishers on mobile apps or websites for our advertisers.

#### **2\. Data collection and collection methods**

The Company does not collect or store personal information that may directly identify a specific individual, such as name, contact, email, date of birth, or health status.

The Company automatically collects the following anonymous data in the process of using the Service to achieve the purposes of Article 3.

– Device identification values and IP addresses defined as non-personal information such as Google Advertising ID (GAID), Android ID, Advertiser Identifier (IDFA), Vendor Identifier (IDFV), etc.

– Locale, language, device manufacturer, device name, communication carrier, OS version, user agent,  package list (the applications and/or processes which are installed or run on your device while the partner app is active or inactive) etc.

– User information provided by partner companies such as User ID.

#### **3\. Purpose of data collection**

The Company uses the collected data for the following purposes:

① Member management, identification and delivering service: We use the IP address assigned to your device to send you requested such as your point information. We use unique identifiers of your device to help us authenticate you as the person who should have access to your Buzzvil Account

② Ad serving: We publish personalized, interest-based ads based on individual interests, preferences, etc., and to analyze the effectiveness of advertising.

③ Customer Support: We respond to customer support requests and help resolve any customer support issues that may arise.

④ Frequency capping: We limit the number of times ads are shown (to prevent you from seeing the same ad multiple times)

⑤ Conversion tracking (allowing you to receive points for participating in ads)

⑥ Fraud Detection and Prevention: We identify invalid clicks (or ad queries) to protect BuzzScreen, Advertisers and Advertising Demand Partners from fraudulent behavior.

⑦ Performance measurement and service fee settlement: We report performance of contracts and settle service fee regarding provisions of services demanded by the users

⑧ Notification: We make notice of function of company sites or applications or matters on policy change

⑨ Marketing activities: We provide information on promotional events as well as opportunity to participate

⑩ Legal Necessity, To comply with applicable laws or legal obligation

⑪ Use of information with the prior consent of the users (for example, utilization of marketing advertisement)

⑫ Improvement of existing services and development of new services

The Company agrees that it will obtain consent from the users if the Company desires to use the information other than those expressly stated in this Policy. 

#### **4\. Cookie, Beacons and Similar Technologies**

The Company may collect collective and impersonal information through ‘cookies’ or ‘web beacons’. 

Cookies are very small text files to be sent to the browser of the users by the server used for an operation of the websites of the Company and will be stored in hard-disks of the users’ computer. A web beacon is a small quantity of code which exists on the websites and e-mails. 

By using web beacons, we may know whether a user has interacted with certain webs or the contents of an email. These functions are used for evaluating, improving services and setting-up users’ experiences so that much-improved services can be provided by the Company to the users.

#### **5\. Your Privacy Controls**

European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, and Switzerland

If you are located in the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, publishers who would like us to serve you personalized ads must first obtain your consent so that Buzzvil and our partners can process your personal data for this purpose. If you provide your consent, we will collect, use, share, and otherwise process all of the personal data described above for the purpose of serving you personalized advertising that Buzzvil and our partners believe is most relevant to you.

If you decide that you do not want a personalized advertising experience, we will not process your personal data for this purpose. For example, we will not collect, use, or share your iOS Identifier for Advertising or Android Advertising Identifier, your precise location data, or your demographic or interest information. However, we can still serve you contextual ads that are targeted to the content or type of app you are using.

You can withdraw your consent to our personalized lockscreen content experience at any time.

Publishers may provide a way for you to withdraw your consent to BuzzScreen Policy directly from within an app. If you withdraw your consent from within an app, we will no longer collect, use, share, or otherwise process personal data from that app to personalize your advertising experience.

Even if you do not consent to a personalized advertising experience, or you later withdraw such consent, we will still process your personal data when necessary to comply with law or to support our legitimate interests, as described below.

We will process personal data as necessary to comply with the law. For example, we will collect your IP address to perform a lookup of your country so that we know whether you are located in the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, but we will truncate your IP address before we process it for this purpose.

The United States and Other Countries

Opt-Out: If you are located in the United States or another country outside the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, and Switzerland, you can opt out of receiving personalized advertising by using your applicable device settings:

On iOS, you may opt out by enabling the “Limit Ad Tracking” setting.

On Android devices, you may opt out by enabling the “Opt out of Ads Personalization” setting.

#### **6\. Sharing your information**

We work with Publisher Partners, Advertising Demand Partners, Supported Advertising Mediation Partners, Data Partners, and Fraud and Measurement Partners (collectively, “Buzzvil Partners”) in order to provide the Buzzvil Services. Unless otherwise noted in our partner list, Buzzvil Partners are each independent controllers of your data. We will provide the current list of Buzzvil Partners with whom we share your data upon request.

In principle, the Company will not share user information to third parties without prior consent. However, we may share data to provide service and comply for the following cases.

– To serve personalized ads from Advertising Demand Partners  
  
– To share aggregated ad performance measurement with advertisers and publishers, process settlement, detect fraudulent activities and manage customer CS response

– In the case of requests from investigative agencies in accordance with procedures and methods set forth in the Act for investigation purposes

– Other cases where the user gives prior consent for sharing his or her personal information

#### **7\. Data security and storage**

The Company takes the security of customer information very seriously. The Company maintains data security through industry-standard security measures, including firewalls and encryption, and keeps data for a period that meets the following requirements:

– To complete the customer support service provided

– To comply with applicable legal and regulatory obligations

– To prevent abuse and use of unauthorized services

– To prevent other disputes, and disputes between users

The company constructs the following security measures to protect the users’ personal information from any unauthorized access, release, use or modification:

– Transmit users’ personal information by using encrypted communication zone

– Store important information such as passwords after encrypting it

– Install a system in the zone the external access to which is controlled so as to prevent leakage or damage of users’ personal information by hacking or computer virus

– Establish and execute internal management plan 

– Operate access control system 

– Take measures to prevent forging or alteration of access record

#### **8\. Global operation and Privacy Shield**

We base our services on AWS solutions, which has already obtained approval from EU data protection authorities, known as the Article 29 Working Party, of the AWS Data Processing Addendum and Model Clauses to enable transfer of data outside Europe, including to the U.S.

#### **9\. Users’ right to access**

The users or their legal representatives, as main agents of the information, may exercise the following options regarding the collection, use and sharing of personal information by the Company: 

– Exercise right to access to personal information

– Make corrections or deletion

– Make temporary suspension of treatment of personal information 

– Request the withdrawal of their consent provided before

If, in order to exercise the above options, you, as an user, contact the Company by using representative telephone or sending a document or e-mails, or using telephone to the responsible department (or person in charge of management of personal information), the Company will take measures without delay: Provided that the Company may reject the request of you only to the extent that there exists either proper cause as prescribed in the laws or equivalent cause. 

If you are located in the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, and withdraw your consent, we will also inform our current partners with whom we have shared the data of your withdrawal or opt-out so that they, as independent controllers of your personal data, can also respect your choice. Our partners may also have separate legal bases for collecting, using, retaining, and sharing your personal data.

#### **10\. Protection of personal information of children**

#### In principle, the Company does not collect any information from the children under 13 or equivalent minimum age as prescribed in the laws in the relevant jurisdiction. The website, products, and services of the Company are the ones to be provided to ordinary people, in principle. The Company does not intentionally collect any personal information from children.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, you must be at least 16 years of age to consent to personalized advertising experience. We do not collect or otherwise process personal data from individuals in the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, and Switzerland whom it knows to be under 16 years of age, except for compliance with a legal obligation and pursuit of a legitimate interest.  
  
We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use Personal Information from children under 16 years of age, and no part of the Service is directed to children under the age of 16. If you learn that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, then you may alert us at [dpo@buzzvil.com](mailto:dpo@buzzvil.com). If we learn that we have collected any Personal Information from children under 16, then we will promptly take steps to delete such information.

#### **11\. Data Protection Officer**

To communicate with our Data Protection Officer, please email [dpo@buzzvil.com](mailto:dpo@buzzvil.com).

#### **12\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

The Company may change its Policy for a variety of reasons, such as improving your personal information processing procedures, reflecting changes to company services, or complying with applicable laws. If the Company changes its Policy, we will notify you using the Service or any other reasonable means. 

#### **13\. Other important information**

① Data transmission: Considering it engages in global businesses, the Company may provide the users’ personal information to the companies located in other countries for the purpose as expressly stated in this Policy. For the places where the personal information is transmitted, retained or processed, the Company takes reasonable measures for protecting that personal information.

② 3rd party’s sites and services: The website, product or service of the Company may include the links to the ones of a 3rd party and the privacy protection policy of the site of the 3rd party may be different. Thus, it is required for the users to check additionally that policy of a 3rd party site linked to the site of the Company.

#### **14\. Responsible department of Company**

The Company designates the following department and person in charge of personal information in order to protect the personal information of customers and deal with complaints from customers: 

E-mail: [support@buzzvil.com](mailto:support@buzzvil.com)

Mail: 3rd Floor, Daelim Building, 272 Seokchon Lake, Songpa-gu, Seoul, Korea

When we receive formal written complaints, we respond by contacting the person who made the complaint. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of your data that we cannot resolve with you directly.

_Application date: May 25th, 2018_
